【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 4]
[4회]
I'm here to discuss with His Majesty
저는 폐하와 논의하기 위해 왔습니다
The alliance between Xunnan and Jialin.
Xunnan과 Jialin의 동맹.
If I married a Jialin woman
내가 가림여자와 결혼한다면
Our alliance will be more stable.
우리 동맹은 더욱 안정될 것입니다.
It turned out to be my senior.
알고 보니 내 선배였다.
I think Miss He is the best candidate
내 생각엔 Miss He가 가장 적합한 후보인 것 같아
For my Princess Yong.
나의 용 공주님을 위해.
That's why he came.
그래서 그가 온 것입니다.
That's why they asked us to bring girls of the same age.
그래서 그들은 우리에게 같은 또래의 소녀들을 데려오라고 요청했습니다.
Prince Yong will choose his wife.
용왕은 그의 아내를 선택할 것입니다.
Prince Yong is indeed a talented , handsome man.
용왕자는 정말 재능있고 잘생긴 남자다.
The girl just returned to the capital
소녀는 방금 수도로 돌아왔다
You have found your perfect husband.
당신은 완벽한 남편을 찾았습니다.
incredible.
믿을 수 없는.
This girl is so successful!
이 소녀는 정말 성공했어요!
Is he kidding?
농담하는 걸까요?
Or is there something wrong with you?
아니면 뭔가 문제가 있는 걸까요?
Your Majesty, we cannot accept his request.
폐하, 우리는 그의 요청을 받아들일 수 없습니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
Don't blame me for what I would say.
내가 말한 것에 대해 나를 비난하지 마십시오.
Wedding rings are a great strategy for our country.
결혼반지는 우리나라를 위한 훌륭한 전략입니다.
Who chooses to join the alliance is critical.
누가 동맹에 가입할지가 중요합니다.
We have to think long term.
우리는 장기적으로 생각해야 합니다.
We must think carefully.
우리는 신중하게 생각해야 합니다.
in my opinion,
내 생각에는,
Ms. He didn't know how to bear such responsibility.
Ms. 그는 그런 책임을 지는 방법을 몰랐습니다 .
Prince Yong, what do you think?
용왕님, 어떻게 생각하시나요?
Please tell us more.
자세한 내용을 알려주세요.
I shouldn't talk about it here.
나는 그것에 대해 여기서 이야기해서는 안됩니다.
And I'm not a snitch.
그리고 나는 밀고자가 아닙니다.
but something
하지만 뭔가
You need to know.
넌 알아야 해.
She learns martial arts
그녀는 무술을 배운다
He has been climbing Mount Wuhua since he was six years old.
그는 6살 때부터 우화산(Wuhua Mountain)을 등반해 왔습니다.
She came back a few months ago.
그녀는 몇 달 전에 돌아왔습니다.
Since her return, she has gotten into a lot of trouble.
그녀가 돌아온 이후로 그녀는 많은 어려움을 겪었습니다.
make the whole city
도시 전체를 만들다
What a mess.
정말 엉망이군요.
Not to mention Thorin.
토린은 말할 것도 없고요.
my son
내 아들
And there are several children of ministers here.
그리고 여기에는 목사의 자녀가 여러 명 있습니다.
Beaten by He Jiuling.
He Jiuling에게 패배했습니다.
This is not true.
이것은 사실이 아닙니다.
gentlemen,
신사,
Even when you're inventing something, you have to be consistent.
무언가를 발명할 때에도 일관성을 유지해야 합니다.
how they were beaten,
그들이 어떻게 구타를 당했는지,
why none of you
왜 너희 중 누구도
tell me?
말해 주세요?
or they think
아니면 그들은 생각한다
Do children deserve to be beaten?
아이들은 구타당할 자격이 있나요?
General He
그 장군
I shouldn't talk,
얘기하면 안 되는데,
But it's true!
하지만 사실이에요!
Zhong Yongjun is bragging.
종용준이 자랑하고 있다.
For example,
예를 들어,
Just a month ago,
불과 한 달 전,
I have carefully cultivated grapes for several years
몇 년 동안 정성스럽게 포도를 재배해 왔습니다
Collected by your dear daughter.
사랑하는 딸이 수집했습니다.
Is that true?
그게 사실인가요?
Those grapes to be sent to the palace
궁으로 보낼 그 포도
-Dad -it's all wasted
- 아빠 - 다 낭비됐어요
- She did it all. - who knows?
- 그녀가 다 해냈어요. - 누가 알아?
Mr. Li,
리 씨,
I compensate you with twelve fine vines
내가 네게 좋은 포도나무 열두 그루로 갚으리라
They must be ripe by now, right?
지금쯤이면 다 익었을 텐데요, 그렇죠?
OK
좋아요
Master.
주인.
So you are the one who sent the vines.
그러므로 포도나무를 보내신 분이 바로 당신이십니다.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
Jiang Rong said you are not coming.
장롱이 당신이 오지 않는다고 하더군요.
Please take a seat.
자리에 앉으세요.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
Mr. Li,
리 씨,
If you have any complaint
불만사항이 있는 경우
Just tell me.
그냥 말해.
No, nothing else.
아니요, 다른 건 없습니다.
I just remembered.
방금 생각났어요.
I don't mean to blame Miss He.
나는 Miss He를 비난하려는 것이 아닙니다.
The vine you sent
당신이 보낸 포도나무
They are now bearing fruit.
그들은 이제 열매를 맺고 있습니다.
I will send the grapes to the palace.
포도를 궁으로 보내겠습니다.
Once they are ripe.
일단 익으면.
I'm waiting for your grapes.
나는 당신의 포도를 기다리고 있습니다.
Yes, Your Majesty.
예, 폐하.
Thank you Mr. Li.
리 선생님께 감사드립니다.
Lorde Zhongyong,
로드 종용(Lord Zhongyong),
Your son is injured
당신의 아들이 다쳤어요
Because he insisted on fighting with Miss He.
왜냐하면 그는 Miss He와의 싸움을 주장했기 때문입니다.
She didn't take the initiative to provoke him.
그녀는 그를 자극하기 위해 솔선하지 않았습니다.
Although my son was injured,
아들이 다쳤는데도
I have paid ten thousand taels of gold
나는 10만 테엘의 금을 지불했습니다
In the name of Miss He.
Miss He의 이름으로.
His son decided to give up.
그의 아들은 포기하기로 결정했습니다.
Still thinking?
아직 생각 중이신가요?
Ten thousand taels of gold?
1만 테엘의 금?
Sim.
심.
As for the others you mentioned,
당신이 언급한 다른 것들에 관해서는,
if someone
만약 누군가가
There are unresolved issues
해결되지 않은 문제가 있습니다
Together with Miss He,
미스헤와 함께,
Or that compensation
아니면 그 보상
This is not enough,
충분하지 않다,
Welcome to come to me.
나에게 오신 것을 환영합니다.
I take responsibility.
나는 책임을 집니다.
No one is asking you to do this.
아무도 당신에게 이것을 하라고 요구하지 않습니다.
it's all my fault.
그것은 모두 내 잘못이야.
I had no idea my daughter did all this.
나는 내 딸이 이 모든 일을 했는지 전혀 몰랐습니다 .
but
하지만
All this has nothing to do with Master Rong.
이 모든 것은 롱 선생님과 아무 관련이 없습니다.
If you encounter problems in the future,
앞으로 문제가 발생하면,
I will handle it.
내가 처리하겠습니다.
The responsibility is all mine.
책임은 모두 내 몫이다.
General He,
그 장군님,
How could it have nothing to do with me?
어떻게 나와 관련이 없을 수 있니?
Miss He is my fiancé.
Miss 그는 내 약혼자예요.
Of course I need to take care of her.
물론 나는 그녀를 돌봐야합니다.
What?
무엇?
Miss He is Lord Rong’s fiancée?
미스 그는 롱 경의 약혼자인가요?
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
I have never heard that Mr. Rong is engaged.
나는 롱씨가 약혼했다는 소식을 들어본 적이 없습니다.
it's a pity.
불쌍해.
How could he marry that girl from the He family?
그가 어떻게 그 집안의 그 소녀와 결혼할 수 있었습니까?
He is not on the same level as her.
그는 그녀와 같은 수준이 아닙니다.
Not a good combination.
좋은 조합은 아닙니다.
completely.
완전히.
Why did he say that?
왜 그런 말을 했나요?
Don't make a big deal out of a molehill.
두더지 언덕에서 큰 일을하지 마십시오.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
i don't even know
나도 모르겠어
You are engaged.
당신은 약혼했습니다.
General, he and my father were friends,
장군님, 그와 아버지는 친구였습니다.
They made a deal when we were kids .
우리가 어렸을 때 그들은 거래를 했어요 .
Miss He left the capital
Miss He는 수도를 떠났어요
I'm busy learning divination,
나는 점술을 배우느라 바쁘다.
no one talks about it,
아무도 그것에 대해 이야기하지 않아요.
But that doesn't mean it doesn't exist
하지만 그렇다고 그것이 존재하지 않는다는 뜻은 아니다
So Prince Yong had to find someone else.
그래서 용왕은 다른 사람을 찾아야 했습니다 .
What do you-
당신은 무엇을-
She is your fiancée.
그녀는 당신의 약혼자입니다.
So you are not married yet.
그럼 아직 결혼하지 않으셨군요.
Since you are not married yet,
아직 결혼하지 않으셨기 때문에
Why can't she marry me?
그 사람은 왜 나와 결혼할 수 없나요?
Xunnan Gan became the vassal state of Jialing.
Xunnan Gan은 Jialing의 가신 국가가되었습니다.
We are committed to opening up various trade routes,
다양한 무역로를 개척해 나가겠습니다.
Send thousands of craftsmen,
수천 명의 장인을 보내십시오.
Share the West Sea and cultivate thousands of hectares of fertile land for Jialin.
서해를 공유하고 수천 헥타르의 비옥한 토지를 지알린(Jialin)을 위해 경작하십시오.
We take this alliance very seriously,
우리는 이 동맹을 매우 진지하게 받아들입니다.
But Jialin didn't even give up on the minister's engagement.
그러나 Jialin은 장관의 약혼 도 포기하지 않았습니다 .
Opening up trade routes can benefit both sides.
무역로를 개방하면 양측 모두에게 이익이 될 수 있습니다.
Your craftsmen can learn our advanced skills.
당신의 장인은 우리의 고급 기술을 배울 수 있습니다 .
Opening up the West China Sea will allow
서중국해를 개방하면
Exchange food with Jialin.
Jialin과 음식을 교환하세요.
This benefits both parties.
이는 양측 모두에게 이익이 됩니다.
Why does Prince Yong think that
용왕님은 왜 그렇게 생각하시나요?
Is Jia Lin the only one who benefits?
Jia Lin만이 혜택을 받는 사람인가요?
They can't show that you value this alliance.
그들은 당신이 이 동맹을 소중히 여긴다는 것을 보여줄 수 없습니다 .
It's just collaboration.
바로 협업입니다.
Moreover, if Jia Lin cancels my engagement
게다가 Jia Lin이 내 약혼을 취소한다면
Xunnan became a vassal state,
순난은 속국이 되었고,
It will also destroy the alliance with Xunnan
또한 Xunnan과의 동맹도 파괴됩니다.
To obtain more benefits in the future.
앞으로 더 많은 혜택을 얻으려면.
Breaking a promise is a taboo in alliances.
약속을 어기는 것은 동맹에서 금기시되는 일이다.
Jia Lin can't do this.
Jia Lin은 이것을 할 수 없습니다.
Prince Yong, your goal is always the highest.
용왕님, 당신의 목표는 언제나 최고입니다.
How could you not know?
어떻게 모를 수가 있니?
What if I insist?
내가 주장하면 어떻게 되나요?
So you can try and see
그래서 당신은 시도하고 볼 수 있습니다
if you could catch my bride
내 신부를 잡을 수 있다면
de Jialin.
드 지알린.
Mr. Rong,
롱 씨,
Are you threatening me?
나를 협박하는 겁니까?
certainly.
틀림없이.
majesty,
위엄,
I am the messenger of Xunnan.
나는 Xunnan의 메신저입니다.
The only condition for forming an alliance with Jialin is marriage.
가림과 동맹을 맺기 위한 유일한 조건은 결혼이다.
if you refuse,
당신이 거절한다면,
We don't need to talk anymore
우리 더 이상 얘기할 필요 없어
Your Highness, please wait a moment.
전하, 잠시만 기다려 주십시오.
We did not receive the order.
우리는 주문을 받지 못했습니다.
Please give me a clear answer, Your Majesty.
명쾌한 답변 부탁 드립니다, 폐하.
majesty.
위엄.
Prince Yong, you have fallen in love with Miss He.
용왕님, 당신은 허씨와 사랑에 빠졌습니다.
But He Jiuling is...
하지만 허지울링은...
Tell Prince Yong
용왕님께 전해주세요
You told me.
당신은 나에게 말했다.
Sim.
심.
Prince Yong,
용왕님,
Therefore,
그러므로,
He even promised this girl,
그 사람은 그 여자한테도 약속했지
I can't accept it.
나는 그것을 받아들일 수 없다.
Besides, you won’t accept it.
게다가 당신은 그것을 받아들이지 않을 것입니다.
As for your future wife,
미래의 아내에 관해서는,
We'll discuss that later.
이에 대해서는 나중에 논의하겠습니다.
I think now,
지금 생각해보면,
You don't want to talk about it.
당신은 그것에 대해 이야기하고 싶지 않습니다.
I'll wait for your private chat.
귀하의 비공개 채팅을 기다리겠습니다.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
Yes, Your Majesty.
예, 폐하.
you are engaged,
당신은 약혼했어요,
But you hid it from me
하지만 당신은 그것을 나에게 숨겼어요
Put me into an embarrassing situation.
나를 난처한 상황에 빠뜨리세요.
I apologize for my mistake.
내 실수에 대해 사과드립니다.
I just found out today,
오늘에서야 알게 됐는데,
I will grant you and He Jiuling a marriage.
나는 당신과 He Jiuling의 결혼을 허락할 것입니다.
what do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
I thank Your Majesty on behalf of my daughter.
제 딸을 대신하여 폐하께 감사드립니다.
Even if you don't want to marry him
그 사람과 결혼하고 싶지 않더라도
Don't create chaos now.
이제 혼란을 일으키지 마십시오.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
Ling, let's go.
링, 가자.
quickly.
빠르게.
Go thank your Majesty.
가서 폐하께 감사드립니다.
Listen, come on.
들어봐, 어서.
He Jiuling,
허 지울링,
A beautiful, smart, educated, dignified girl.
아름답고, 똑똑하고, 교육받고, 품위 있는 소녀.
The two must choose an auspicious day to get married.
두 사람은 결혼하기 위해 상서로운 날을 선택해야 한다.
Announce it to the world, let everyone know.
세상에 알리고 모두에게 알려주세요.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
Your Highness.
전하.
Do you know Prince Yong?
용왕님을 아시나요?
He is my senior.
그는 나의 선배입니다.
I just found out today that he is Prince Yong.
오늘에서야 그 사람이 용왕자라는 걸 알았습니다 .
Ling,
링,
Things have reached this point and there is no turning back.
상황이 이 지점에 도달했으며 되돌릴 수 없습니다.
Just accept it.
그냥 받아들이세요.
Your Majesty, you have not been in good health recently.
폐하께서는 최근 건강이 좋지 않으셨습니다.
This also worries me.
이 점 역시 걱정스럽습니다.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
Your Highness.
전하.
Two men fight over a woman. What a show!
두 남자가 한 여자를 두고 싸운다. 정말 멋진 쇼였습니다!
Excellent.
훌륭한.
My experience with my sister was eye-opening.
언니와의 경험은 정말 놀라웠습니다.
That's why I like women.
그래서 나는 여자를 좋아한다.
It's a pity that I am too young.
제가 너무 어려서 안타깝습니다.
Otherwise I will also participate in the competition
그렇지 않으면 나도 대회에 참가할 것이다
Fight against Prince Yong and Duke Rong.
용왕과 용공과 싸워라.
Your Highness, stop playing with me.
전하, 저랑 장난치지 마세요.
I was serious.
나는 진지했다.
This is serious.
이건 심각해.
But Mr. Rong is a good man.
하지만 롱 씨는 좋은 사람이에요.
I'm very happy with this agreement.
나는 이번 계약에 매우 만족한다.
Although I can't marry you
비록 당신과 결혼할 수는 없지만
When you have a daughter in the future
나중에 딸 낳으면
I married her.
나는 그녀와 결혼했습니다.
I know from what happened today
오늘 무슨 일이 있었는지 알아
The sooner you get engaged, the better.
약혼은 빨리할수록 좋습니다.
This is a dragon pendant given to me by my father.
이것은 아버지께서 주신 용 펜던트입니다.
Represent the emperor.
황제를 대표합니다.
stand up. I'm not done yet.
일어서세요. 난 아직 안 끝났어.
This pendant represents the emperor.
이 펜던트는 황제를 상징합니다.
With him around, no one dares to stop him anywhere.
그와 함께라면 어느 누구도 감히 그를 막을 수 없습니다.
Acceptance as a symbol of my future wife .
미래의 아내의 상징으로 받아들여짐 .
My engagement is not yet confirmed.
아직 약혼이 확정되지 않았습니다.
It's too early to talk about my daughter.
내 딸에 대해 이야기하기에는 너무 이르다.
I cannot accept this symbol.
나는 이 상징을 받아들일 수 없습니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I heard my father say
나는 아버지가 말씀하시는 것을 들었다.
maybe ten months from now
아마도 지금으로부터 10개월 후에
Your baby is born.
당신의 아기가 태어났습니다.
Take it.
가져.
my future mother-in-law
내 미래의 시어머니
I'm going to take a nap now.
저는 이제 낮잠을 자려고 합니다.
As a father,
아버지로서,
I can't believe I didn't find out
내가 그걸 알아내지 못했다니 믿을 수 없어
Everything Ling has done in the capital so far.
Ling이 지금까지 수도에서 한 모든 일.
I'm sorry you got involved in this.
당신이 이 일에 연루되어서 미안해요.
I'm happy to help you.
기꺼이 도와드리겠습니다.
Now I feel worse.
이제 기분이 더 나빠졌습니다.
It seems
것 같다
long ago, the emperor
오래 전, 황제
Marry Ling to Prince Yong.
링(Ling)과 용왕(Yong Prince)과 결혼하세요.
if not you
당신이 아니라면
Ling may have been sent to Xunnan.
Ling이 Xunnan으로 보내졌을 수도 있습니다.
I will never see her again in this life.
나는 이생에서 그녀를 다시는 볼 수 없을 것입니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
I'm not talking about this.
나는 이것에 대해 말하는 것이 아닙니다.
I'm talking about the general.
나는 장군에 대해 이야기하고 있습니다.
I have accepted this position.
나는 이 입장을 받아들였습니다.
I know you made a mistake
나는 당신이 실수했다는 것을 알아요
So I came to the palace to report
그래서 보고하러 궁에 왔어요
General He, Assistant Minister He.
허 장군, 허 차관.
His Majesty summoned the two of them to the royal study.
폐하께서는 두 사람을 왕실 연구실로 부르셨습니다.
As a general, you will be sent to guard Nanjiang.
장군으로서 당신은 난장을 지키도록 파견될 것입니다.
You must say no.
아니오라고 대답해야합니다.
If you don't do this,
이렇게 하지 않으면
The He family is very powerful;
He 가족은 매우 강력합니다.
Ministers will be jealous of me.
장관들이 나를 질투할 것이다.
So the whole He family...
그래서 He 가족 전체가...
General He.
장군 그.
Why do I feel that Ms. He is not happy?
나는 왜 그 씨가 행복하지 않다고 느끼는가 ?
The emperor granted her a marriage. What a blessing!
황제는 그녀에게 결혼을 허가했습니다. 얼마나 큰 축복입니까!
Miss He loves you very much.
Miss 그는 당신을 매우 사랑합니다.
Shouldn't she be happy?
그녀는 행복해야 하지 않나요?
Mr. Rong, what do you think is going on?
롱씨, 무슨 일이 일어나고 있다고 생각하시나요?
Mr. Rong.
롱 씨.
Your Majesty, they have arrived.
폐하, 그들이 도착했습니다.
- Get fired. - Yes.
- 해고되세요. - 예.
He Liang.
허 리앙.
Yes, Your Majesty.
예, 폐하.
I offended Prince Yong because of He Jiuling.
나는 He Jiuling 때문에 Yong Prince를 화나게했습니다.
I think even if the alliance is formed
제 생각 엔 동맹이 성립되더라도
It must be unwilling.
그럴 의지가 없어야 합니다.
I plan to give you an important mission
나는 너에게 중요한 임무를 줄 생각이다.
and held their ground in Nanjiang
난장(Nanjiang)에 자리를 잡았습니다.
Curb south-seeking.
남쪽 추구를 억제하십시오.
This is a great honor for the He family
이것은 He 가족에게 큰 영광입니다
Let us serve Jialin and His Majesty.
Jialin과 폐하를 섬기자.
But my father is forty
하지만 아버지는 마흔 살이세요.
He is no longer the staunch warrior who fought alongside His Majesty before.
그는 더 이상 이전에 폐하와 함께 싸웠던 확고한 전사가 아닙니다.
Maybe he can't bear such a big responsibility.
어쩌면 그는 그렇게 큰 책임을 질 수 없을지도 모릅니다.
to alleviate His Majesty's concerns.
폐하의 걱정을 덜어드리기 위해.
I've thought about this too.
나도 이것에 대해 생각했습니다.
Unfortunately,
안타깝게도,
There is no better candidate.
더 나은 후보는 없습니다.
General Yan Zhao of the left, with a keen mind,
왼쪽의 Yan Zhao 장군은 예리한 마음으로
He is a man of skill and strategy.
그는 기술과 전략을 갖춘 사람입니다.
He fought under my father for many years.
그는 내 아버지 밑에서 수년 동안 싸웠습니다.
I believe he can do this.
나는 그가 이것을 할 수 있다고 믿습니다.
The right general Fu Rongde is good at training troops.
오른쪽 장군 푸롱더(Fu Rongde)는 군대를 훈련하는 데 능숙합니다.
And smart and brave.
그리고 똑똑하고 용감해요.
The soldiers he trained could each face three opponents.
그가 훈련한 병사들은 각각 세 명의 적과 맞붙을 수 있었습니다.
I think he can do it too.
내 생각엔 그 사람도 할 수 있을 것 같아.
He Liang, what do you think?
He Liang, 어떻게 생각하세요?
European Union...
유럽 ​​연합...
I think
제 생각에는
What Chenzhou said makes sense.
Chenzhou의 말은 일리가 있습니다.
I will think about it fondly.
소중히 생각하겠습니다.
It's all my incompetence's fault
다 내 무능력 탓이야
I have betrayed His Majesty's trust.
나는 폐하의 신뢰를 배반했습니다.
As for the position of general,
장군의 입장을 말하자면,
I hope His Majesty can recover it.
폐하께서 회복하실 수 있기를 바랍니다.
I don't deserve her.
나는 그녀를받을 자격이 없습니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
This is the He family’s century-old battlefield loyalty
이것이 허 가문의 100년 된 전장 충성심 이다
This allowed the Xuanyuan family to sit on the throne.
이로 인해 Xuanyuan 가족이 왕좌에 앉을 수 있었습니다.
As long as the Xuanyuan family exists,
Xuanyuan 가족이 존재하는 한,
Just like the He family.
He 가족처럼요.
As for the position of general,
장군의 입장을 말하자면,
Even if you don't go to Nanjiang, it's worth a visit.
난장에 가지 않더라도 방문할 가치가 있습니다.
Moreover, only the He family
게다가 He 가족만이
Worthy of her.
그녀에게 합당합니다.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
[Royal Library]
[왕립도서관]
When the home
집에 있을 때
keep away
멀리하다
Serving the country?
국가에 봉사하는가?
we always
우리는 항상
Willing to die for the emperor.
황제를 위해 기꺼이 죽겠습니다.
And died for the country.
그리고 나라를 위해 죽었습니다.
However,
하지만,
We have to be unthinking.
우리는 생각하지 말아야 합니다.
your mother died
네 엄마가 돌아가셨어
To save your sister.
언니를 구하기 위해.
Your sister has been ill for six years
네 여동생은 6년 동안 병을 앓았어
And he was treated in Wuhua Mountain for ten years.
그리고 그는 오화산에서 10년 동안 치료를 받았습니다.
Now,
지금,
Life finally took a turn for the better.
인생은 마침내 더 나은 방향으로 바뀌었습니다.
She is getting married.
그녀는 결혼한다.
I couldn't stand it if something happened to her.
그녀에게 무슨 일이 생기면 참을 수 없었습니다.
I don't want her involved
나는 그녀가 연루되는 것을 원하지 않는다
There is no risk at all.
전혀 위험이 없습니다.
Ms. He.
그 씨.
you need to be so proud
넌 정말 자랑스러워해야 해
After getting engaged to Master Rong?
Master Rong과 약혼한 후?
Can you at least be polite?
최소한 예의를 갖추실 수 있나요?
- proudly? - It is clear.
- 자랑스럽게요? - 분명해요.
Mr. Rong's graceful manner is impressive.
롱 씨의 우아한 태도가 인상적입니다.
the best.
최고.
Now he is with you.
이제 그는 당신과 함께 있습니다.
I didn't say a word in the palace.
나는 궁전에서 한마디도하지 않았습니다.
what did I do?
내가 뭘 한거지?
Are you deaf or blind?
당신은 귀머거리입니까 아니면 시각 장애인입니까?
Mr. Rong was right all along
Rong 씨는 줄곧 옳았습니다
But you took advantage of the engagement
하지만 당신은 약혼을 이용했어요
and spent the whole evening with him.
저녁 내내 그와 함께 보냈습니다.
Isn't that true?
그렇지 않나요?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Stop pretending
척은 그만해
Everyone knows what happened between you and Mr. Rong.
당신과 롱 씨 사이에 무슨 일이 일어났는지 모두가 알고 있습니다.
Inside Rong Mansion.
롱 맨션 내부.
looking at you.
너를보고있는.
- who do you think You Are? - stop.
- 당신은 누구라고 생각하나요? - 멈추다.
- No one in the capital thinks - enough is enough.
- 수도의 어느 누구도 충분하다고 생각하지 않습니다.
You are attractive.
당신은 매력적입니다.
Finally someone is willing to talk to you.
마침내 누군가가 기꺼이 당신과 이야기를 나눌 것입니다.
And he even forced Master Rong to marry him.
그리고 그는 심지어 Rong Master에게 자신과 결혼하도록 강요했습니다.
Use this dirty trick.
이 더러운 속임수를 사용하십시오.
i know i'm scared
나도 알아 내가 무서워
Even the servants were sent away.
하인들도 쫓겨났습니다.
How embarrassing!
정말 당황스럽네요!
I didn't send it.
나는 그것을 보내지 않았다.
No?
아니요?
Do
하다
Master Rong forced him
Rong 선생님이 그를 강요했습니다.
Spend the night with him?
그 사람과 하룻밤을 보낼까?
If I hadn't forced Mr. Rong
내가 롱씨를 강요하지 않았다면
sleep with you,
너랑 자고,
How could Duke Rong risk offending the envoy?
용공 이 어떻게 사신을 모욕할 위험을 감수할 수 있겠습니까?
Is it responsible for you?
그게 당신 책임인가요?
Do you think he really likes you?
그 사람이 정말 당신을 좋아하는 것 같나요?
- Keep dreaming. - let's go. let's go.
- 계속 꿈을 꾸세요. - 갑시다. 갑시다.
You are so shameless.
당신은 너무 뻔뻔해요.
It also annoyed King Xunnan.
그것은 또한 Xunnan 왕을 짜증나게 했습니다.
I think
제 생각에는
You were born a bitch.
당신은 개년으로 태어났습니다.
Now that you know what kind of person I am,
이제 내가 어떤 사람인지 알았으니
How dare you provoke me?
어떻게 감히 나를 자극합니까?
Today I will teach you a lesson.
오늘 나는 당신에게 교훈을 가르쳐 줄 것입니다.
Shi Jin is very direct.
시진은 매우 직접적이다.
Miss He, don't be angry.
Miss He, 화내지 마세요.
Shijin, pare de falar.
Shijin, pare de falar.
If you dare to hurt me, my father will not let you go.
네가 감히 나를 해친다면 내 아버지는 너를 가만두지 않을 것이다.
how old are you?
몇 살이에요?
You should fight me.
당신은 나와 싸워야합니다.
Come. let's go. let's go.
오다. 갑시다. 갑시다.
If you don't want to get hit, watch what you say.
맞고 싶지 않다면 말을 조심하세요.
Everyone in the capital knows it.
수도에 있는 사람들은 모두 그것을 알고 있습니다.
Can you shut everyone up?
다들 입 다물게 해줄 수 있어?
You did something inappropriate to Lord Rong.
당신은 롱 경에게 부적절한 짓을 했습니다.
- Now he's angry with us. - Exactly.
- 이제 그는 우리에게 화를 냈습니다. - 정확히.
enough.
충분한.
Rong Yu
유 롱
Ms. He,
그 씨,
You took advantage of the engagement
당신은 약혼을 이용했습니다
I spent the whole evening with him.
나는 저녁 내내 그와 함께 보냈다.
Everyone knows what happened between you and Mr. Rong.
당신과 롱 씨 사이에 무슨 일이 일어났는지 모두가 알고 있습니다.
-You have no shame. ——Rongfu.
-당신은 부끄러움이 없습니다. ——롱푸.
I heard my father say
나는 아버지가 말씀하시는 것을 들었다.
Maybe, ten months later,
아마도 10개월 뒤에는
Your baby is born.
당신의 아기가 태어났습니다.
Rong Yu!
유롱!
Rong Yu, saia.
롱 유, 사이아.
Ms. He.
그 씨.
Miss He, don't be rude.
Miss He, 무례하게 굴지 마세요.
I need to talk to him now.
지금 그 사람과 얘기를 좀 해야 해요.
I will defeat anyone who tries to stop me.
나를 막으려는 자는 누구든지 물리칠 것이다.
You caused a commotion last night.
당신은 어젯밤에 소란을 일으켰습니다.
Say no more.
더 말하지 마.
Zhanping,
잔핑,
Do you remember what I said?
내가 무슨 말을 했는지 기억하시나요?
I remember.
기억해.
Miss He, what's wrong?
Miss He, 무슨 일이야?
Miss He, where are we going?
Miss He, 우리 어디로 가는 거죠?
Heshan, Zhanping, don’t come with me.
허산, 잔핑, 나와 함께 가지 마세요.
No need to drag me. I will go with you.
나를 끌 필요가 없습니다. 나는 당신과 함께 갈 것입니다.
You follow them. I'm looking for General He.
당신은 그들을 따릅니다. 나는 He 장군을 찾고 있어요.
I? Is he sure?
나? 그 사람이 확실한가요?
If Miss He bullies Mr. Rong
Miss He가 Rong 선생님을 괴롭히면
Should I save or not?
저장해야 하나 말아야 하나?
You decide.
당신이 결정합니다.
Ms. He.
그 씨.
Miss He, please let me go first.
미스 씨, 나 먼저 가게 해주세요.
I need a room.
방이 필요해요.
Second floor. Lotus Room.
2 층. 로터스룸.
Miss He...
미스 그...
Did God send them?
하나님이 그들을 보내셨나요?
- Quickly. - Miss He.
- 빠르게. - 미스 헤.
Somewhere in between.
그 사이 어딘가.
【Lotus Room】
【로터스룸】
I asked you before
아까 물어봤잖아
If you planned to propose to the emperor, but you refused.
황제에게 청혼하려고 했으나 거절한 경우 .
Don't like looking at stars?
별 보는 걸 좋아하지 않나요?
Why not stay at Astrology Pavilion?
Astrology Pavilion에 묵어보시는 건 어떨까요 ?
Why did you go to the palace?
왜 궁에 가셨나요?
Don't say you went there to eat.
거기 먹으러 갔다고 말하지 마세요.
I'm looking for General He.
나는 He 장군을 찾고 있어요.
Do you think I would believe it?
내가 믿을 것 같나요?
As the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion,
Xingxiang Pavilion의 젊은 스승으로서,
How dare you frame me?
감히 나를 모함하는 건 어때?
Make arrangements for you?
당신을 위해 준비를 하시겠습니까?
Although she is not a virtuous woman,
비록 덕이 있는 여자는 아니지만,
Never thought I would be
내가 그럴 거라고는 생각도 못 했어
The target of these rumors.
이 소문의 대상은.
why did you decide
왜 결정했어?
take me to your home
나를 당신 집으로 데려가 주세요
Did you take off your clothes yesterday?
어제 옷을 벗었나요?
You misunderstood...
당신은 오해했습니다 ...
You got it wrong.
당신이 틀렸어요.
Where are the two people who just came in?
방금 들어온 두 사람은 어디에 있나요?
Second floor. Lotus Room.
2 층. 로터스룸.
- Go to Heshan. - correct.
- 허산으로 가세요. - 옳은.
Who are you?
누구세요?
We don't allow three people to share a room.
우리는 세 사람이 방을 공유하는 것을 허용하지 않습니다 .
- This is-- - This is Mr. Rong's bag.
- 이것은... - 이것은 롱 선생님의 가방입니다.
This is the money the girl gave me
이건 그 여자가 나한테 준 돈이야
Take all the gold. I just need this bag.
금을 모두 가져가세요. 나한테는 이 가방이 필요할 뿐이야.
I feel lucky today.
오늘은 운이 좋은 것 같아요.
He's making things up.
그는 일을 꾸미고 있습니다.
My brother cares about me very much.
내 동생은 나에게 많은 관심을 가지고 있습니다.
Why doesn't he take me home?
그 사람은 왜 나를 집에 데려가지 않는 걸까요?
If you say your people hurt me
당신의 사람들이 나에게 상처를 입혔다고 말하면
How could he ignore me?
그 사람이 어떻게 나를 무시할 수 있겠어요?
this time,
이 시간,
It was my fault.
그것은 내 잘못이었습니다.
I'll clarify this.
나는 이것을 명확히 할 것이다.
clarify? for what?
밝히다? 무엇 때문에?
Who will believe you?
누가 당신을 믿을 것인가?
Rong Yu, no need to clarify.
윤용님, 굳이 설명할 필요가 없습니다.
Let us be together.
우리 함께하자.
Anyway, my reputation is already very bad.
어쨌든 내 평판은 이미 매우 나빴습니다.
Don't think you can get away with it.
당신이 그것에서 벗어날 수 있다고 생각하지 마십시오.
enough.
충분한.
I'm a man.
나는 남자입니다.
I might lose control.
나는 통제력을 잃을 수도 있습니다.
Do you think I have anything to lose by taking this job?
내가 이 일을 하면 잃을 것이 있다고 생각하시나요 ?
Even if I did something to you
내가 너한테 무슨 짓을 했어도
At worst, I'd be Montutus,
최악의 경우, 나는 Montutus가 될 것입니다.
Rather than being meticulous and respectful
꼼꼼하고 예의 바르기보다는
Master celebrity collector.
유명인 수집가의 대가.
The world is crueler to women
세상은 여자에게 더 잔인하다
Compared with men.
남자와 비교하면.
If you really want to put down the blade,
정말로 칼날을 내려놓고 싶다면 ,
People will look down on you and hurt you.
사람들은 당신을 무시하고 상처를 줄 것입니다.
Although I want to enlighten you and protect you,
너를 깨우치고 보호하고 싶어도
I can not do anything.
나는 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
Did I ask you to protect me?
내가 보호해달라고 했나요?
Why are you doing all this?
왜이 모든 일을하고 있습니까?
Why did you give them grapes and money?
왜 그들에게 포도와 돈을 주었나요?
He wanted to limit me until we got married.
그는 우리가 결혼할 때까지 나를 제한하고 싶었습니다.
Rong Yu, I don’t want to marry you.
용우 씨, 나는 당신과 결혼하고 싶지 않아요.
But you write to me every day.
그런데 당신은 나에게 매일 편지를 씁니다.
Said he wanted to meet under the moonlight.
달빛 아래서 만나고 싶다고 하더군요.
I'm looking forward to our meeting.
나는 우리의 만남을 고대하고 있습니다.
He told me he missed me and thought I was crazy.
그는 내가 보고 싶었고 내가 미쳤다고 생각했다고 말했습니다 .
I just want to ask you out
난 그냥 너한테 데이트 신청하고 싶어
say clearly
명확하게 말하다
And please ask my father to cancel the engagement.
그리고 아버지께 약혼을 취소해달라고 부탁하세요.
You gave me your Turkish horse,
당신은 나에게 터키 말을 주었습니다.
This is his favorite.
이것은 그가 가장 좋아하는 것입니다.
My father stole something from me.
아버지가 나에게서 뭔가를 훔쳤어요.
- You even- - Rong Yu, that's enough.
- 너도 - - 롱 유, 그만해요.
Since I started learning martial arts,
무술을 배우기 시작한 이후로
i never thought about my husband
난 내 남편에 대해 생각해 본 적이 없어
I would be a weak person like you.
나도 너처럼 약한 사람이 될 텐데.
You know nothing about my preferences.
당신은 내 취향에 대해 아무것도 모릅니다.
I don't know what you like.
당신이 무엇을 좋아하는지 모르겠어요.
If we are always together,
늘 함께라면
None of us will be happy.
우리 중 누구도 행복하지 않을 것입니다.
I told you not to like me
나 좋아하지 말라고 했잖아
I made it very clear.
나는 그것을 매우 명확하게 만들었습니다.
Why don't you understand?
왜 이해하지 못해요?
He Jiuling,
허 지울링,
I thought
나는 생각했다
It was a meaningless drunken chat.
의미 없는 술취한 잡담이었다.
European Union -
유럽 ​​연합 -
- Dad - He Jiuling, what are you doing?
- 아빠 - He Jiuling, 뭐하는거야?
You are a disgrace.
당신은 불명예입니다.
- You idiot. - It's not her fault. it's me.
- 당신은 바보. - 그 사람 잘못이 아니예요. 나야.
Rong Yu, get out of the way.
롱 유, 비켜라.
I have to teach her a lesson today.
나는 오늘 그녀에게 교훈을 가르쳐야 한다.
Dad, I'm sorry.
아빠, 미안해요.
I didn't touch him.
나는 그를 만지지 않았습니다.
Do you have any plans...
혹시 계획 있으신가요...
This annoys me.
이것은 나를 짜증나게 한다.
——General He. - Dad, wait. listen to me.
——그 장군. - 아빠, 잠깐만요. 내 말을 들어보세요.
Pai County,
파이 카운티,
Let’s take Ling home first.
먼저 링을 집에 데려가자.
Mr. Rong also needs to take care of himself.
Rong 씨도 자신을 돌봐야합니다.
Don't let anyone see the mess.
누구도 혼란스러운 모습을 볼 수 없도록 하세요.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
I'll be sure to give an explanation.
제가 꼭 설명을 해드리겠습니다.
Come home with me quickly.
나랑 빨리 집에 가세요.
let's go.
갑시다.
Heshan,
허샨,
Don't let anyone spread rumors.
누구도 소문을 퍼뜨리지 못하게 하세요.
- Quickly. - Yes.
- 빠르게. - 예.
Mr. Rong, you told me
롱 씨, 당신이 말했잖아요
If Miss He bothers you, leave her.
Miss He가 당신을 괴롭히면 그녀를 떠나십시오.
I shouldn't be involved.
나는 관여해서는 안 된다.
That's why I didn't go in.
그래서 나는 들어가지 않았다.
【He Mansion】
【히 맨션】
Kneel down.
에 무릎을 꿇고 앉다.
Pass the baton to He Chenzhou.
허첸저우에게 지휘봉을 넘겨주세요.
Dad, do you really want to hit her?
아빠, 정말 때리고 싶어요?
Now she actually dares to bully a man.
이제 그녀는 실제로 감히 남자를 괴롭힌다.
From now on you can kill people and set fires.
이제부터 사람을 죽이고 불을 지를 수 있습니다.
hurry up.
서둘러요.
you idiot,
당신은 바보,
Won't you irritate me?
나를 짜증나게 하지 않을래?
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
What happened, Dad?
무슨 일이 있었나요, 아빠?
It's none of your business. Return to the room.
너와는 상관 없어. 방으로 돌아갑니다.
help me.
도와주세요.
My father would kill me.
아버지는 나를 죽일 것입니다.
How dare you ask for help?
어떻게 감히 도움을 요청합니까?
If Rong Yu hadn’t let you go
용우가 당신을 보내지 않았다면
You're not going to kneel now.
이제 무릎을 꿇지 않을 것입니다.
will it be me
나야?
Kneel at the door of Rong Mansion.
롱 맨션(Rong Mansion) 문 앞에 무릎을 꿇으십시오.
Dad, the engagement has been decided.
아빠, 약혼이 결정됐어요.
It's only a matter of time before this happens.
이런 일이 발생하는 것은 시간문제일 뿐입니다.
it's not a big deal.
그것은 큰 문제가 아닙니다.
you are mean,
너 나빠,
How can you say that?
어떻게 그런 말을 할 수가있어?
European Union-
유럽 ​​연합-
I'll finish you too
나도 끝내줄게
Dad, they are really gone,
아빠, 정말 사라졌어요
This means Rong Yu is already with us.
이는 Rong Yu가 이미 우리와 함께 있다는 것을 의미합니다.
Not what you want?
당신이 원하는 것이 아닌가요?
Don't you just want to make sure they're married?
단지 그들이 결혼했는지 확인하고 싶지 않나요 ?
This is what you want.
이것이 당신이 원하는 것입니다.
Dad, I'm sorry.
아빠, 미안해요.
- I'll never do it again. - She said she would never do it again.
- 다시는 안 그럴 거예요. - 다시는 그러지 않겠다고 하더군요.
I will draw a clear line with Rong Yu.
나는 Rong Yu와 명확한 선을 긋겠습니다.
I will never tease or piss you off again.
나는 다시는 당신을 놀리거나 화나게 하지 않을 것입니다.
He Jiuling, you can't escape
He Jiuling, 당신은 벗어날 수 없습니다
This beating today.
오늘은 이 구타.
your -
당신의 -
group.
그룹.
She's sorry, Dad.
미안해요, 아빠.
I will beat you until you die.
나는 당신이 죽을 때까지 당신을 이길 것입니다.
Dad, if you hurt her,
아빠, 만약 당신이 그녀를 다치게 했다면,
Rong Yu will cancel the wedding.
Rong Yu는 결혼식을 취소합니다.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Father, father.
아버지, 아버지.
help me.
도와주세요.
Stop running. return!
달리기를 멈추세요. 반품!
I want you to learn
나는 당신이 배우기를 바랍니다
-Dad -you fool
-아빠 -바보야
How dare you run away?
어떻게 감히 도망칠 수 있나요?
Volt.
볼트.
You won't get away with this.
당신은 이것으로 도망치지 않을 것입니다.
Go away.
저리 가요.
-Dad
-아빠
- dad - get out
- 아빠 - 나가
Since I started learning martial arts,
무술을 배우기 시작한 이후로
i never thought about my husband
난 내 남편에 대해 생각해 본 적이 없어
It's a weakling like you.
너 같은 약자야.
You know nothing about my preferences.
당신은 내 취향에 대해 아무것도 모릅니다.
I don't know what you like.
당신이 무엇을 좋아하는지 모르겠어요.
If we are always together,
늘 함께라면
None of us will be happy.
우리 중 누구도 행복하지 않을 것입니다.
I told you not to like me
나 좋아하지 말라고 했잖아
I made it very clear. Why don't you understand?
나는 그것을 매우 명확하게 만들었습니다. 왜 이해하지 못해요?
How should I accept your gift?
당신의 선물을 어떻게 받아들여야 할까요?
Please get up.
일어나주세요.
on that day,
그날에,
I made a mistake
제가 실수를
Let Miss He stay in Rong Mansion.
Miss He를 Rong Mansion에 머물게 해주세요.
I'm here to apologize today.
오늘은 사과하러 왔습니다.
Why are you apologizing?
왜 사과하는 거야?
If anyone is guilty, it's our fault.
누군가 유죄라면 그것은 우리의 잘못이다.
Yesterday Ling was severely punished by me.
어제 Ling은 나에게 심한 처벌을 받았습니다.
I grounded her too
나도 그녀를 접지시켰어
Let her reflect.
그녀가 반성하게 해주세요.
Isn’t it a bit harsh?
좀 심하지 않은가?
my Lord.
군주.
Rong Yu is a member of this family.
Rong Yu는 이 가족의 일원입니다.
bell tower.
종탑.
Miss He can't leave,
Miss 그는 떠날 수 없어요
She is in a bad mood
그녀는 기분이 좋지 않다
and refused to eat.
그리고 식사를 거부했습니다.
what do I do?
나는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
For a warrior, missing a few meals is not a problem at all.
전사에게는 몇 끼의 식사를 거르는 것이 전혀 문제가 되지 않습니다.
But what...
근데 뭐...
Don't bother me with these things anymore.
더 이상 이런 일로 나를 괴롭히지 마세요.
You can leave now.
지금 떠나셔도 됩니다.
Sim.
심.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
I'm not just doing this for you.
나는 단지 당신을 위해 이 일을 하는 것이 아닙니다.
I also taught my daughter.
나는 또한 내 딸에게도 가르쳤습니다.
Stop begging.
구걸하지 마세요.
For my troubled daughter.
고민하는 딸을 위해.
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 석양 아래♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 너 같은 사람을 기다리며 조용히 시타르를 연주한다 ♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫